<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on C101 Friday Hongtao</title>
    <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on C101 Friday Hongtao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://c1010.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Third Week Class (Monday (1/27)</title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/review/3rd-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/review/3rd-week/</guid>
      <description>Quiz Link to the 3rd_week_quiz
Note Reading For this week: McChesney: Policing the Unthinkable. Read it carefully by yourself because questions in midterm and in final exam come from both weekly lectures and reading assignments.
Topic: Media owenership Good source of information is important for people to elect for the President.
Media conglomerates are a result of deregulation of media business.
Possible negative influences of concentrated media ownership  Harm to the economy and society; Increase in barriers for new companies; Powerful will filter out information they do not like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Second Week Class (Wednesday (1/21)</title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/review/2nd-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/review/2nd-week/</guid>
      <description>Quiz Link to the 1st_and_2nd_week_quiz
Media Literacy The ability to access, analyze, evaluate, create, and act using all forms of communication.
Access   old times: radio, newspaper, TV, &amp;hellip;
  now: digital divide
  Analyze The foundation of media analysis is acknowledging that all media is constructed with a purpose and a particular point of view. Renee Hobbs:
 who created this message and what is the purpose?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of First Week Class (Wednesday (1/15)</title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/review/1st-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/review/1st-week/</guid>
      <description>Quiz Link to the 1st_and_2nd_week_quiz
Some wrong comments:  Media is biased Too much violence in the media Too much media usage make people anti-social &amp;hellip; All in all, technology is not the problem. It is how people use it that causes problems.  Difference between &amp;ldquo;media&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;the media&amp;rdquo;: The media: people will associate negative things with &amp;ldquo;the media&amp;rdquo;
Media is a plural of medium. It is wrong to term the &amp;ldquo;media&amp;rdquo; so broadly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Week_Media Journal_Due on Jan 24th 7 a.m.</title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/assignments/media-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/assignments/media-journal/</guid>
      <description>Due: Friday, Jan. 24, 7 a.m., (before your discussion section) Best Practice: Think about the assignment prior to Jan. 17 discussion section so if needed, you can ask questions about the assignment during discussion. Submission: Upload to Canvas You can download this template: Template You can download this example: Example  Description: For this short project you will track your media consumption for 24 hours. In your journal, keep track of what media you consume, how it is paid for (both direct and indirect funding), and what technologies/platforms you use to consume it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/anthony-%E6%95%99%E6%8E%88%E6%BC%94%E8%AE%B2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/anthony-%E6%95%99%E6%8E%88%E6%BC%94%E8%AE%B2/</guid>
      <description>Trump Twitter
Is Twitter a public forum? Can private platforms be public forums?
Information servis providers vs telecommunications services
Open Internet Order</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/week2-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/week2-3/</guid>
      <description>week 2-3 Guest Speaker Media Journal assignment
Media Placement Exam (MPE)&amp;ndash; Next Friday For potential journalism majors.
  Once you post your material, audiences will interpret in their own ways.
  Media literary: transforming info into knowledge
  Law of closure
  Filter bubble
  confirmation bias
  information satisficing
  All media are constructed with a purpose and a particulur point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/week3-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/week3-1/</guid>
      <description>Reading For this week: McChesney: Policing the Unthinkable
Topic: Media owenership Good source of information is important for people to elect for the President. Media conglomerates is a result of deregulation of media business. Possible negative influences of concentrated media ownership:  Harm to the economy and society; Increase in barriers for new companies; Powerful will filter out information they do not like.  Possible benefits of concentrated ownership:  Overall economy gets strengthended when individual companies become stronger; Larger companies have the power to battle unfair government leaders and policies whereas smaller media organizations do not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/week4-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/week4-3/</guid>
      <description>The first amendment
Internet History:
Arpanet Tim Berners-Lee Mosaic
Five freedoms guaranteed by the First Amendment? religion, speech, press, assemble, petition</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/%E6%88%91%E6%95%B4%E7%90%86%E7%9A%84%E7%AC%AC%E4%BA%8C%E5%91%A8%E7%9A%84%E8%A7%86%E9%A2%91%E5%86%85%E5%AE%B9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/%E6%88%91%E6%95%B4%E7%90%86%E7%9A%84%E7%AC%AC%E4%BA%8C%E5%91%A8%E7%9A%84%E8%A7%86%E9%A2%91%E5%86%85%E5%AE%B9/</guid>
      <description>discuss media journal assignment neilson report prepare them for media placement exam
tell students to read articles for monday &amp;amp; wednesday
send prof. conway the two questions by next monday.
Media Literacy: The ability to access, analyze, evaluate, create, and act using all forms of communication.
Access: digital divide
analyze: The foundation of media analysis is acknowledging that all media is constructed with a purpose and a particular point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/%E9%99%A2%E9%95%BF%E6%BC%94%E8%AE%B2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/notes/%E9%99%A2%E9%95%BF%E6%BC%94%E8%AE%B2/</guid>
      <description> Unwarranted conspiracy theories (UCTs):   AN EXPLANATION THAT RUNS COUNTER TO SOME RECEIVED, official, or obvious account;  Paranoid style  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>