<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assignments on C101 Friday Hongtao</title>
    <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/assignments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assignments on C101 Friday Hongtao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://c1010.netlify.com/assignments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5th Week_News_Lead_Due on Feb 17th 7 a.m.</title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/assignments/news-lead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/assignments/news-lead/</guid>
      <description>Due: Monday, Feb. 17, 7:00 a.m. Best Practice: Draft it prior to Friday Discussion Section (Feb. 14th) Submission: Upload to Canvas Read this excert of Tim Harrower&amp;rsquo;s textbook Inside Reporting: Harrower excerpt  Your task: As a journalist, it is your role to gather background information about your story’s subject in order to ask informed questions and write a comprehensive, accurate account.
  Gather background information on the Cuban Center at IU, enough to give you the necessary context to understand the press conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Week_Media Journal_Due on Jan 24th 7 a.m.</title>
      <link>https://c1010.netlify.com/assignments/media-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c1010.netlify.com/assignments/media-journal/</guid>
      <description>Due: Friday, Jan. 24, 7 a.m., (before your discussion section) Best Practice: Think about the assignment prior to Jan. 17 discussion section so if needed, you can ask questions about the assignment during discussion. Submission: Upload to Canvas You can download this template: Template You can download this example: Example  Description: For this short project you will track your media consumption for 24 hours. In your journal, keep track of what media you consume, how it is paid for (both direct and indirect funding), and what technologies/platforms you use to consume it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>